Rud Stanislav

Trainee/Junior Front-end Developer

Day of birthday: 31 July 1990

City: Kharkov

Email: rudstanislav1990@gmail.com

Site: stanislavrud.github.io/cv_v4

Skype: zevas_2140

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/stanislav-rud-527357111

Summary:

Hello, my name is Stanislav Rud. I looking for my first job as a Trainee / Junior Front-End developer. I have small, non-commercial experience in developing websites, landing pages, I have HUGE desire to develop, improve and continue! Use my skills in real projects!

More than 3 years of experience working with hosts on such platforms as: ESXI, Hyper-V, Proxmox, more 1.5 years deploying web servers on Apache24, Ngnix, ISS, and their support. Introduced Jira CRM system to provide user support from developers. Configured the monitoring system. Debugged the servers. Worked with servers as Supermicro, Dell, IBM, Cloud QNAP.

In free time, I create single-page websites according to layouts. Learn React, JS, TypeScript, English, Also I constantly improve my skills in website development.

I have an understanding and basic experience working with such assemblers as Gulp, Webpack, Grunt, React.

Have experience with WebStorm, VSCode, Emmet, Photoshop, Figma.

Work Experience:

(2018 – today) System Administrator, GROUP OF COMPANIES "FACTOR"

- ✓ Server management, workstations, routers, switches and existing network applications.
- ✓ Monitoring and daily system checks.
- ✓ Diagnostics and resolving various technical issues related to hardware and software.
- ✓ Support for all network systems LAN, WAN.
- ✓ Ensuring network security and integrity.
- ✓ Backup, data recovery in case of failures or other situations, system and data recovery.

(2015 – 2018) System Administrator, Chain of supermarkets «CHUDO»

- ✓ Server management, workstations, computers, laptops, printers, routers, switches and existing network applications.
- ✓ Monitoring and daily system checks.
- ✓ Diagnostics and resolving various technical issues related to hardware and software.
- ✓ Laying, construction, support of all network systems LAN, WAN.
- ✓ Ensuring security and integrity of the network.
- ✓ Backup, data recovery in case of failures or other situations, system and data recovery.
- ✓ Opening new branches, shops.
- ✓ Connecting and configuring commercial equipment.



- ✓ Remote user support.
- ✓ Working with users.
- ✓ Tenders and contracts with equipment suppliers

Education:

KHAI - (2007 - 2011)

Bachelor – Engineer Constructor Aircrafts and Helicopters.

KHAI - (2011 - 2013)

Specialist – Aircraft Testing and Certification.

Additional Education:

Telesens Academy (2015)

QA Core (manual testing WEB, mobile, desktop, UI, checklist, test cases, bug-report) **NT School** (2018)

Front-End developer (HTML5/CSS3/SCSS/Flex-box/Grid CSS).

A-Level (2018 – 2019)

Full Stack (HTML5/CSS3/Flex-Box/JS/Git).

Skills:

- ✓ HTML5/CSS3, SCSS (Responsive, Adaptive)
- ✓ JavaScript, Bootsrap, JQuery (Plagins)
- ✓ Adobe Photoshop, Figma
- ✓ Version Control (Git)
- ✓ Virtualizations (VMware Workstation, Hyper-V, Proxmox, ESXI)
- ✓ Active network equipment (MikroTik, Ubiquiti, Fortigate, HP)
- ✓ Windows servers
- ✓ Linux systems, servers
- √ Web Servers (Apache24, Nginx, IIS)
- ✓ Database (MS SQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL)
- ✓ CRM (Jira, Mantis, Bitrix24, 1C)
- ✓ Hardware (Supermicro, Dell, IBM, QNAP)

Additional information:

Currently, I am working as a System Administrator, but I really want to change my profession and start a career as a Front-End Developer.

- ✓ Quickly learning
- ✓ Initiative
- ✓ Executive
- ✓ Punctual
- √ Hard-working
- ✓ Responsible
- ✓ Great desire to learn and develop to front-end development